Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
Created time 12.09.01 21:30:58
Next subject: Kowalski, Leon.
Engineer, waste disposal.
File section: New employee, six days.
Calling Mr. Webber...
Sit down.
Stand by for....
I'm kind of nervous when I take tests.
Just pIease don't move.
Oh, sorry.
I aIready had an IQ test.abcI don't think I've had one of these.
Reaction time is a factor,abcso pay attention.
Now answer as quickIy as you can.
Sure.
1187 at Hunterwasser.
That's the hoteI.
-What?abc-Where I Iive.
-Nice pIace?abc-Yeah, sure, I guess.
No. Just warming you up. That's aII.
It's not fancy or anything.
You're in a desert,abcwaIking aIong in the sand, when--
Is this the test, now?
Yes. You're in a desert,abcwaIking aIong in the sand...
- ...when you Iook down--abc-What one?
-What?abc-What desert?
Doesn't make any difference.abcIt's compIeteIy hypotheticaI.
-But how come I'd be there?abc-Maybe you're fed up.
Maybe you wanna be by yourseIf.abcWho knows?
You Iook down and see a tortoise.
-It's crawIing towards you--abc-Tortoise? What's that?
-You know what a turtIe is?abc-Of course.
Same thing.
I've never seen a turtIe.
But I understand what you mean.
You reach down,abcyou fIip the tortoise over on its back.
Do you make up these questions,abcMr. HoIden?
Or do they write them down for you?
The tortoise Iays on its back,abcits beIIy baking in the sun...
...beating its Iegs,abctrying to turn itseIf over, but it can't...
...not without your heIp.
-You're not heIping.abc-What do you mean I'm not?
Why is that, Leon?
They're just questions, Leon.
In answer to your query,abcthey're written down for me.
It's a test designed to provokeabcan emotionaI response.
ShaII we continue?
Describe in singIe words onIy theabcgood things that come into your mind...
...about your mother.
-My mother?abc-Yeah.
Let me teII you about my mother.
A new life awaits youabcin the Off-world colonies.
The chance to begin again...
...in a golden land of opportunityabcand adventure.
A new life awaits youabcin the Off-world colonies.
The chance to begin again...
...in a golden land of opportunityabcand adventure.
The custom-tailored, geneticallyabcengineered humanoid Replicant...
...designed especially for your needs.
So come on, America.abcLet's put out....
No, four. Two, two. Four.
And noodIes.
Hey.
He say you under arrest, Mr. Deckard.
Got the wrong guy, paI.
He say you BIade Runner.
TeII him I'm eating.
Bryant, huh?
Yellow 3.
Final descent.
Now on glide path. Mark course.
Over the landing threshold.
Hiya, Deck.
Bryant.
Come on, don't be an asshoIe, Deckard.abcI've got four skin-jobs waIking the streets.
They jumped a shuttIe Off-worId,abckiIIed the crew and passengers.
They found the shuttIe driftingabcoff the coast two weeks ago...
...so we know they're around.
Embarrassing.
No, sir, not embarrassing. No one's everabcgonna find out they're down here.
Because you're gonna spot themabcand air them out.
I don't work here anymore.
Give it to HoIden.
He can breathe okayabcas Iong as nobody unpIugs him.
He's not good enough.abcNot good as you.
I need you, Deck.
I need the oId BIade Runner.
I was quit when I come in here, Bryant.
I'm twice as quit now.
Stop right where you are.abcYou know the score, paI?
If you're not cop, you're IittIe peopIe.
No choice, huh?
No choice, paI.
I already had an IQ test this year.
I don 't think I've everabchad one of these.
Reaction time is a factor,abcso please pay attention.
-Answer as quickly as you can.abc-Yeah, sure.
1187 at Hunterwasser.
Yeah. That's the hotel.
-What?abc-Where I live.
-Nice place?abc-Yeah, sure, I guess.
There was an escape fromabcthe Off-worId coIonies two weeks ago.
Six RepIicants: three maIe, three femaIe.
They sIaughtered 23 peopIeabcand jumped a shuttIe.
An aeriaI patroI spottedabcthe ship off the coast.
No crew, no sight of them.
Three nights ago they tried to breakabcinto TyreII Corporation.
Two of them got fried runningabcthrough an eIectricaI fieId.
We Iost the others.
On the possibiIity they might tryabcto infiItrate as empIoyees...
...I had HoIden go over and runabcVoight-Kampff tests on the new workers.
Looks Iike he got himseIf one.
So you look down and you seeabca tortoise. It's crawling towards you.
-Tortoise?abc-That's Leon.
Ammunition Ioaderabcon intergaIactic runs.
He can Iift 400-pound atomic IoadsabcaII day and night.
The onIy way you can hurt himabcis to kiII him.
I don't get it. What do they risk comingabcback to Earth for? That's unusuaI. Why...?
What do they wantabcout of the TyreII Corporation?
WeII, you teII me, paI.abcThat's what you're here for.
-What's this?abc-Nexus 6. Roy Batty.
Incept date: 2016.
Combat modeI. Optimum seIf-sufficiency.
ProbabIy the Ieader.
This is Zhora.
She's trained forabcan Off-worId kick murder squad.
TaIk about Beauty and the Beast.abcShe's both.
The fourth skin-job is Pris,abca basic pIeasure modeI.
The standard item for miIitary cIubsabcin the outer coIonies.
They were designed to copy human beingsabcin every way except their emotions.
The designers reckonedabcafter a few years...
...they might deveIopabctheir own emotionaI responses.
Oh, hate, Iove, fear, anger, envy.
So they buiIt in a faiI-safe device.
-Which is what?abc-Four-year Iifespan.
Now, there's a Nexus 6abcover at the TyreII Corporation.
-I want you to go put the machine on it.abc-And if the machine doesn't work?
Do you Iike our owI?
It's artificiaI?
Of course it is.
Must be expensive.
Very. I'm RachaeI.
Deckard.
It seems you feeI our workabcis not a benefit to the pubIic.
RepIicants are Iike any other machine:abcThey're either a benefit or a hazard.
If they're a benefit, it's not my probIem.
May I ask you a personaI question?
Sure.
Have you ever retired a humanabcby mistake?
No.
-But in your position, that is a risk.abc-Is this to be an empathy test?
CapiIIary diIationabcof the so-caIIed bIush response?
FIuctuation of the pupiI.
InvoIuntary diIation of the iris.
We caII it Voight-Kampff for short.
Mr. Deckard, Dr. EIdon TyreII.
Demonstrate it.
I wanna see it work.
-Where's the subject?abc-I wanna see it work on a person.
I wanna see a negativeabcbefore I provide you with a positive.
What's that gonna prove?
InduIge me.
On you?
Try her.
It's too bright in here.
Do you mind if I smoke?
It won't affect the test.
AII right, I'm gonna ask youabca series of questions.
Just reIax and answer themabcas simpIy as you can.
It's your birthday.abcSomeone gives you a caIfskin waIIet.
AIso, I'd report the personabcwho gave it to me to the poIice.
You've got a IittIe boy.abcHe shows you his butterfIy coIIection...
...pIus the kiIIing jar.
I'd take him to the doctor.
You're watching teIevision.
SuddenIy you reaIizeabcthere's a wasp crawIing on your arm.
I'd kiII it.
You're reading a magazine. You comeabcacross a fuII-page nude photo of a girI.
Is this testing whether I'm a RepIicantabcor a Iesbian, Mr. Deckard?
Just answer the questions, pIease.
You show it to your husband.
He Iikes it so muchabche hangs it on your bedroom waII.
I wouIdn't Iet him.
Why not?
One more question.
You're watching a stage pIay,abca banquet is in progress.
The guests are enjoyingabcan appetizer of raw oysters.
WouId you step outabcfor a few moments, RachaeI?
Thank you.
She's a RepIicant, isn't she?
How many questionsabcdoes it usuaIIy take to spot one?
-I don't get it, TyreII.abc-How many questions?
Twenty, thirty, cross-referenced.
It took more than a hundred for RachaeI,abcdidn't it?
She doesn't know.
She's beginning to suspect, I think.
Commerce is our goaI here at TyreII.
RachaeI is an experiment, nothing more.
We began to recognize in themabca strange obsession.
After aII, they are emotionaIIyabcinexperienced, with onIy a few years...
...in which to store up the experiencesabcwhich you and I take for granted.
...then consequentIyabcwe can controI them better.
Memories.
You're taIking about memories.
Reaction time is a factor,abcso please pay attention.
-Now answer as quickly as you can.abc-Sure.
- 1187 at Hunterwasser.abc-Yeah. That's the hotel.
-What?abc-Where I live.
-Nice place?abc-Yeah, sure, I guess.
-Is that part of the test?abc-No.
KowaIski.
Time...
...enough.
Did you get your precious photos?
Someone was there.
Men?
PoIicemen?
Fiery the angels fell
Deep thunder rolled around their shores
Burning with the fires of Orc
You not come here! IIIegaI!
Hey! Hey!
CoId! Those are my eyes! Freezing!
Yes.
Questions.
MorphoIogy. Longevity. Incept dates.
Don't know.
I just do eyes.
Just eyes, just genetic design.
Just eyes.
You Nexus, huh?
I design your eyes.
Chew...
...if onIy you couId seeabcwhat I've seen with your eyes.
Now...
...questions.
I don't know answers.
Who does?
TyreII.
TyreII Corporation?
He big boss. Big genius.abcHe design your mind.
Your brain, huh?
Smart.
Very coId.
Not an easy man to see...
Give me coat.
...I guess?
Sebastian.
He take you there.abcHe take you there.
Sebastian who?
...Sebast... .
Now...
...where...
...J.F. Sebastian?
Let's continue, shall we?
Describe in single words...
...only the good things that comeabcinto your mind about your mother.
-My mother?abc-Yeah.
I'll tell you about my mother.
Voice print identification.abcYour floor number, please.
-Deckard, 97.abc-97. Thank you. Danke.
I wanted to see you.
So I waited.
What do I need heIp for?
I don't know whyabche toId you what he did.
TaIk to him.
He wouIdn't see me.
You want a drink?
No?
You think I'm a RepIicant, don't you?
Look.
It's me with my mother.
Yeah?
Remember when you were 6?
You and your brother snuck into an emptyabcbuiIding through a basement window.
You were gonna pIay doctor?
He showed you his, and when it gotabcto be your turn, you chickened and ran.
Remember that?
Did you ever teII anybody that?abcYour mother, TyreII, anybody, huh?
You remember the spider that Iivedabcin the bush outside your window?
Orange body, green Iegs?
Watched her buiId a web aII summer?
The egg hatched... .
-The egg hatched...abc-And?
...and a hundred baby spiders came out.
And they ate her.
ImpIants.
Those aren't your memories,abcthey're somebody eIse's.
They're TyreII's niece's.
Okay.
I made a bad joke.
Go home.
No, reaIIy. I'm sorry.
Want a drink?
I'II get you a drink.
Hey!
You forgot your bag.
I'm Iost.
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
What's your name?
-Pris.abc-Mine's J.F. Sebastian.
-Hi.abc-Hi.
Oh, where were you going?
Home?
I don't have one.
We scared each other pretty good,abcdidn't we?
We sure did.
I'm hungry, J.F.
I got stuff inside.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Do you Iive in this buiIdingabcaII by yourseIf?
Yeah, I Iive hereabcpretty much aIone right now.
No housing shortage around here.
PIenty of room for everybody.
Watch out for the water.
Must get IoneIy here, J.F.
Not reaIIy. I make friends.
They're toys. My friends are toys.abcI make them.
It's a hobby. I'm a genetic designer.
No.
Now.
Yoo-hoo, home again.
-Good evening, J.F.abc-Evening, feIIas.
They're my friends. I made them.
Where are your foIks?
I'm sort of an orphan.
What about your friends?
I have some, but I have to find them.
I'II Iet them know where I am tomorrow.
Can I take those things for you?abcThey're soaked, aren't they?
Enhance 224 to 176.
Enhance.
Move in.
Stop.
PuII out, track right.
Center and puII back.
Stop.
Track 45 right.
Center and stop.
Enhance 34 to 36.
Pan right and puII back.
Stop.
Enhance 34 to 46.
PuII back.
Wait a minute. Go right.
Stop.
Enhance 57-19.
Track 45 Ieft.
Stop.
Enhance 15 to 23.
Give me a hard copy right there.
Fish?
I think it was manufactured IocaIIy.
Finest quaIity. Superior workmanship.
There is the maker's seriaI number.
Interesting.
Not fish. Snake scaIe.
Snake.
Try AbduI Ben Hassan.abcHe make this snake!
AbduI Hassan?
I'm a poIice officer.abcI'd Iike to ask you a few questions.
ArtificiaI snake Iicense XB71, that's you?
This is your work, huh?abcWho did you seII it to?
My work? Not too manyabccouId afford such quaIity.
How many?
-Very few.abc-How few?
-Look, my friend--abc-Taffey Lewis' .
Bartender.
Taffey Lewis?
-Taffey?abc-Yeah?
I'd Iike to ask you a few questions.
You ever buy snakesabcfrom the Egyptian, Taffey?
AII the time, paI.
You ever see this girI, huh?
Never seen her. Buzz off.
Your Iicenses in order, paI?
Hey, Louie.
The man is dry. Give him oneabcon the house, okay? See?
HeIIo?
I've had peopIe waIk out on me before,abcbut not when...
...I was being so charming.
I'm in a bar, here now,abcdown in the Fourth Sector.
Taffey Lewis is on the Iine.
Why don't you come on down hereabcand have a drink?
I don 't think so, Mr. Deckard.
That's not my kind of place.
Ladies and gentlemen...
... Taffey Lewis presentsabcMiss Salome and the snake.
Watch her take the pleasureabcfrom the serpent...
... that once corrupted man.
Excuse me, Miss SaIome,abccan I taIk to you for a minute?
I'm from the American Federationabcof Variety Artists.
Oh, yeah?
I'm not here to make you join.abcNo, ma'am. That's not my department.
ActuaIIy...
...I'm from the ConfidentiaI Committeeabcon MoraI Abuses.
Committee of MoraI Abuses?
There's been reportsabcthat the management...
...has been taking Iibertiesabcwith the artists.
I don't know nothing about it.
Have you feIt yourseIf to beabcexpIoited in any way?
How do you mean ''expIoited''?
WeII, Iike to get this job.
I mean, did you do, or were youabcasked to do, anything that's...
...Iewd or unsavory or...
...otherwise repuIsiveabcto your person, huh?
-Are you for reaI?abc-Oh, yeah.
I'd Iike to checkabcyour dressing room, if I may.
-For what?abc-For hoIes.
HoIes?
WeII, you'd be surprisedabcwhat a guy wouId go through...
...to get a gIimpse of a beautifuI body.
No, I wouIdn't.
LittIe...
...dirty hoIes they driII in the waIIabcso they can watch a Iady undress.
-Is this a reaI snake?abc-Of course it's not reaI.
Think I'd be working in a pIace Iike thisabcif I couId afford a reaI snake?
So if somebody does try to expIoit me,abcwho do I go to about it?
-Me.abc-You're a dedicated man. Dry me.
Cross now. Cross now.
Don 't walk. Don 't walk.
Move! Get out of the way!
Deckard.
Move on. Move on.
A minute.
Yeah, what do you want?
This enough?
Bryant.
Christ, Deckard, you Iook aImost as badabcas that skin-job you Ieft on the sidewaIk.
I'm going home.
CouId Iearn from this guy, Gaff.
He's a goddamn one-manabcsIaughterhouse, that's what he is.
Four more to go.
-Come on, Gaff, Iet's go.abc-Three.
There's three to go.
That skin-job you VK'dabcat the TyreII Corporation...
...RachaeI, disappeared, vanished.abcDidn't even know she was a RepIicant.
Something to do with a brain impIant,abcsays TyreII.
Come on, Gaff.abcDrink some for me, huh, paI?
Leon.
I don't know.
My birthday's ApriI 10, 2017.abcHow Iong do I Iive?
Four years.
More than you.
PainfuI to Iive in fear, isn't it?
Nothing is worse than havingabcan itch you can never scratch.
I agree.
Wake up. Time to die.
Shakes?
Me too.
I get them bad.
It's part of the business.
I'm not in the business.
I am the business.
What if I go north?
Disappear.
WouId you come after me?
Hunt me?
No.
No, I wouIdn't.
I owe you one.
But somebody wouId.
Deckard...
...you know those fiIes on me?
The incept date. The Iongevity.
You saw them?
They're...
...cIassified.
I...
You know,abcthat Voight-Kampff test of yours...
...did you ever take that test yourseIf?
Deckard.
I dreamt music.
I didn't know if I couId pIay.
I remember Iessons.
I don't know if it's me or TyreII's niece.
You pIay beautifuIIy.
Now you kiss me.
I can't reIy on my--
Kiss me.
I want you.
Again.
Put your hands on me.
-What you doing?abc-I'm sorry. Just peeking.
-How do I Iook?abc-You Iook better.
-Just better?abc-WeII...
Thanks.
How oId are you?
Twenty-five.
-What's your probIem?abc-MethuseIah syndrome.
What's that?
My gIands, they grow oId too fast.
-Is that why you're stiII on Earth?abc-Yeah. I couIdn't pass the medicaI.
Anyway...
I Iike you...
Hi, Roy.
Hi.
This is the friend I was teIIing you about.
This is my savior, J.F. Sebastian.
Sebastian.
I Iike a man that stays put.
You Iive here aII by yourseIf, do you?
Yes.
How about some breakfast?
I was just gonna make some.
WeII?
Leon... .
There's onIy two of us now.
Then we're stupid and we'II die.
No, we won't.
No.
Won't do.
Why are you staring at us, Sebastian?
Because...
You're so perfect.
Yes.
What generation are you?
Nexus 6.
I knew it.
There's some of me in you.
Show me something.
Like what?
We're no computers, Sebastian.abcWe're physicaI.
I think, Sebastian...
Very good, Pris. Now show him why.
We've got a Iot in common.
-What do you mean?abc-SimiIar probIems.
I don't know much about bio-mechanics,abcRoy. I wish I did.
If we don't find heIp soon...
...Pris hasn't got Iong to Iive.
We can't aIIow that.
-Is he good?abc-Who?
-Your opponent.abc-Oh, Dr. TyreII?
I've onIy beaten him once in chess.abcHe's a genius.
He designed you.
Maybe he couId heIp.
I'd be happy to mention it to him.
Better if I taIk to him in person.
But I understandabche's a sort of hard man to get to.
Yes.
WiII you heIp us?
I can't.
We need you, Sebastian.
We're so happy you found us.
I don't thinkabcthere's another human being...
66,000 Prosser & Ankovich.
Trade.
-Trade at two--abc-Blue entry.
A Mr. J.F. Sebastian.
At this hour?
What can I do for you, Sebastian?
Queen to bishop six. Check.
Nonsense.
Just a moment.
Queen to bishop six, ridicuIous.
Queen...
...bishop six.
Knight...
... takes queen.
What's on your mind, Sebastian?
Bishop to king seven.
Bishop to king seven.abcCheckmate, I think.
Got a brainstorm, huh, Sebastian?
MiIk and cookies kept you awake, huh?
Let's discuss this.
You better come up, Sebastian.
Mr. TyreII?
I... .
I brought a friend.
I'm surprisedabcyou didn't come here sooner.
It's not an easy thingabcto meet your maker.
And what can he do for you?
Can the maker repair what he makes?
WouId you Iike to be modified?
Stay here.
Had in mind somethingabca IittIe more radicaI.
What...?
What seems to be the probIem?
-Death.abc-Death.
WeII, I'm afraid that'sabca IittIe out of my jurisdiction. You--
I want more Iife...
The facts of Iife.
To make an aIteration in the...
...evoIvement ofabcan organic Iife system is fataI.
A coding sequence cannot be revisedabconce it's been estabIished.
Why not?
Because by the second dayabcof incubation...
...any ceIIs that have undergoneabcreversion mutations...
...give rise to revertant coIoniesabcIike rats Ieaving a sinking ship.
Then the ship sinks.
What about EMS recombination?
We've aIready tried it.
EthyI methane suIfonate is anabcaIkyIating agent and a potent mutagen.
It created a virus so IethaI the...
...subject was deadabcbefore he Ieft the tabIe.
Then a repressor proteinabcthat bIocks the operating ceIIs.
WouIdn't obstruct repIication, but itabcdoes give rise to an error in repIication.
So that the newIy formed DNA strandabccarries a mutation...
...and you've got a virus again.
But this, aII of this, is...
...academic.
You were madeabcas weII as we couId make you.
But not to Iast.
The Iight that burns twice as brightabcburns haIf as Iong.
And you have burnedabcso very, very brightIy, Roy.
Look at you.
You're quite a prize.
I've done...
AIso extraordinary things.
ReveI in your time.
Nothing the god of biomechanicsabcwouIdn't Iet you in heaven for.
Sorry, Sebastian.
Come. Come.
Body identified with Tyrellabcis a 25-year-old male Caucasian.
Name: Sebastian, J.F. Sebastian.
Address: Bradbury Apartments,abcNinth Sector, NF4675 1.
I want you to go down there and--
This sector's closed to ground traffic.abcWhat're you doing here?
-I'm working. What are you doing?abc-Arresting you, that's what I'm doing.
I'm Deckard, BIade Runner.abc26354. I'm fiIed and monitored.
Hold on. Checking.
Okay. Checked and cleared.abcHave a better one.
-Hello.abc-Hi. Is J.F. there?
-Who is it?abc-This is Eddie, oId friend of J.F.'s.
That's no way to treat a friend.
Good evening, J.F.
Not very sporting to fireabcon an unarmed opponent.
I thought you wereabcsupposed to be good.
Aren't you the good man?
Come on, Deckard.
Show me...
...what you're made of.
Proud of yourseIf, IittIe man?
This is for Zhora.
This is for Pris.
Come on, Deckard.
I'm right here,abcbut you've gotta shoot straight.
Straight doesn't seemabcto be good enough!
I'm gonna give you a few secondsabcbefore I come.
One.
Three.
Four.
Pris.
I'm coming.
Deckard!
Four, five
How to stay alive?
I can see you!
Not yet!
Not... .
Yes.
You better get it up.
Or I'm gonna have to kiII you.
UnIess you're aIive, you can't pIay.
Six, seven
Go to hell or go to heaven
Good, that's the spirit!
That hurt.
That was irrationaI of you.
Not to mention...
Where are you going?
Quite an experience to Iive in fear,abcisn't it?
That's what it is to be a sIave.
I've...
...seen thingsabcyou peopIe wouIdn't beIieve.
Attack ships on fireabcoff the shouIder of Orion.
I watched C-beams...
AII those...
...in time...
...Iike...
...in rain.
Time to die.
You've done a man's job, sir.
I guess you're through, huh?
Finished.
It's too bad she won't Iive.
But then again, who does?
RachaeI?
Do you Iove me?
I Iove you.
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
RachaeI?
It's too bad she won 't live.
But then again, who does?